A Guide to the Robert and Wilva Breen Collection, 1933-1980
George Mason University Libraries
- The Robert Breen Collection
  - FIRST NATIONAL THEATER ASSEMBLY (REPORT)., Folder 14 (Box Box 102)
  - ANTA REGIONS MAY, 1951., Folder 15 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS - BREEN RESIGNATION., Folder 16 (Box Box 102)
  - ANTA BOARD MEETING 7/16/51., Folder 17 (Box Box 102)
  - TELEGRAM - HOBE MORRISON TO HELEN HAYES 7/51., Folder 18 (Box Box 102)
  - CORRESPONDENCE - RE: WARNER WATSON., Folder 19 (Box Box 102)
  - LETTER - HALL JOHNSON TO BREEN 11/29/51., Folder 20 (Box Box 102)
  - LETTER - MILROY INGRAM TO FRED O'NEAL 2/20/52., Folder 21 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS - "ANTA IN DESPERATE STRAITS" 11/11/53., Folder 22 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS - EUROPE "SKIN OF OUR TEETH" WITH HELEN HAYES., Folder 23 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS - EUROPE "SKIN OF OUR TEETH" WITH HELEN HAYES., Folder 24 (Box Box 102)
  - FREE AND EASY / BLUES OPERA., Folder 25 (Box Box 102)
  - WHO'S BEJART., Folder 26 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS 1937, 1951, 1961 - 62., Folder 27 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS 1963., Folder 28 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS 1964, 1965, 1966., Folder 29 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS 1967, 1968, 1969., Folder 30 (Box Box 102)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS 1971, 1973, 1974, 1976., Folder 31 (Box Box 102)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - UNDATED (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 1 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - UNDATED (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 2 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1938 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 3 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1944 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 4 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1944 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 5 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1945 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 6 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1945 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 7 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1947 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 8 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1948 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 9 (Box Box 103)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE - 1951 (PHOTOCOPIED)., Folder 10 (Box Box 103)
  - BARRYMORE (JOHN)., Folder 1 (Box Box 104)
  - SOUTHERN TOUR (1934 - 1935)., Folder 2 (Box Box 104)
  - FAUST 1935., Folder 3 (Box Box 104)
  - OXFORD PLAYERS., Folder 4 (Box Box 104)
  - AMACO, IVORY DOOR, OXFORD PLAYERS., Folder 5 (Box Box 104)
  - HAMLET, MINNESOTA., Folder 6 (Box Box 104)
  - FINE ARTS LEGISLATION: H.R. 8132, H.J. RES. 671, 1937, 1938., Folder 7 (Box Box 104)
  - CORRESPONDENCE: 1942 - 1946., Folder 8 (Box Box 104)
  - JAVITS, MISC., Folder 9 (Box Box 104)
  - RESIGNATION 7/16/51., Folder 10 (Box Box 104)
  - CORRESPONDENCE: BREEN TO DOWLING 6/27/51., Folder 11 (Box Box 104.)
  - ANTA, NEWS CLIPPINGS: NATIONAL ENDOWMENT FOR THE ARTS., Folder 12 (Box Box 104)
  - PHONE LOG: 7/1/58 - 10/14/58., Folder 13 (Box Box 104)
  - FILM (MARKETING - NYU) '69 WILVA NOTES., Folder 14 (Box Box 104)
  - NOTES TO SELF (1970)., Folder 15 (Box Box 104)
  - ELLINGTON, DUKE., Folder 16 (Box Box 104)
  - "TOM PAINE" - CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 17 (Box Box 104)
  - HARBURG E. Y. - CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 18 (Box Box 104)
  - HOLBROOK HALL`/6/75., Folder 19 (Box Box 104)
  - "THE ELEPHANT MAN", 1979., Folder 20 (Box Box 104)
  - BREEN ROBERT: GUGGENHEIN FELLOWSHIP, 1982., Folder 21 (Box Box 104)
  - ARLEN - MELFI (CORRESPONDENCE)., Folder 22 (Box Box 104)
  - ESCAPE: BREEN ARTICLE 2/87., Folder 23 (Box Box 104)
  - TELEGRAM: 3/12/90 BREEN TO SAMMY DAVIS, Jr., Folder 24 (Box Box 104)
  - NOTEBOOK: "THE ROBERT BREEN COLLECTION"., Folder 25 (Box Box 104)
  - SPEECH: YURIY P. CYIZHIC, CELEBRATION FOR ROBERT BREEN, 5/1/90., Folder 26 (Box Box 104)
  - GOV'T ARTS FUNDING NEA - NORMAN COUSINS 1990., Folder 27 (Box Box 104)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER., Folder 1 (Box Box 105)
  - PROGRAM: JOUVET DES FEMMES, 1951., Folder 2 (Box Box 105)
  - PHOTOGRAPHIC LOAN SERVICE (PHOTOGRAPHS RETURNED)., Folder 3 (Box Box 105)
  - PHOTOGRAPHIC LOAN SERVICE (LOAN RECORDS, 1966)., Folder 4 (Box Box 105)
  - PHOTOGRAPHIC LOAN SERVICE (LOAN RECORDS 1963 - 1964)., Folder 5 (Box Box 105)
  - LETTER: DAVIS TO BREEN, N.D., Folder 6 (Box Box 105)
  - MISC. NEWS CLIPPINGS: ANTA, Folder 7 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA: NEWSLETTERS, MISC 1950s., Folder 8 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA: NATIONAL ASSEMBLY CORRESPONDENCE, 1951., Folder 9 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA: BOARD MINUTES, 1951 - 52., Folder 10 (Box Box 105)
  - AUDIENCES: ANTA., Folder 11 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA, PUBLIC RELATIONS (SCRAPBOOK)., Folder 12 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA ORGANIZATIONAL CHART., Folder 13 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA STAFF (5/51) ORIGINALS IN PRESERVATION BOX., Folder 14 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA: FINANCIAL., Folder 15 (Box Box 105)
  - ANTA: CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 16 (Box Box 105)
  - GERSHWIN, GEORGE: "PORGY AND BESS"., Folder 17 (Box Box 105)
  - "PROGY AND BESS" (1951 - 1956)., Folder 18 (Box Box 105)
  - "PROGY AND BESS" PROGRAMS AND PLAYHILL., Folder 19 (Box Box 105)
  - "PROGY AND BESS", REVIEWS., Folder 20 (Box Box 105)
  - FILM PROJECTS., Folder 1 (Box Box 106)
  - MISS HARGVEAVES II., Folder 2 (Box Box 106)
  - WELLES, ORSON RE: KING LEAR TO RUSSIA - 1956., Folder 3 (Box Box 106)
  - LETTER RE: MARY ROSE., Folder 4 (Box Box 106)
  - PLAY SERIES: GUEST PRODUCER CONTRACTS BLUE LIGHT, GETTING MARRIED., Folder 5 (Box Box 106)
  - DONALD OENSLAGER., Folder 6 (Box Box 106)
  - ADAM'S APPLE., Folder 7 (Box Box 106)
  - ADAM THE CREATOR., Folder 8 (Box Box 106)
  - BUTTON - BUTTON TREATMENT #1 FOR A FILM BY LEONARD LESLEY., Folder 9 (Box Box 106)
  - CYPIAN'S PRAYER., Folder 10 (Box Box 106)
  - THE FIFTH HORSEMAN., Folder 11 (Box Box 106)
  - LET'S DANCE., Folder 12 (Box Box 106)
  - MISCELLANEOUS SCRIPTS: (ABSENT MINDED, BURY THE DEAD ETC., Folder 13 (Box Box 106)
  - PADRIAC THE HERO SCRIPT., Folder 1 (Box Box 107)
  - TAIL WAGS DOG SCRIPT., Folder 2 (Box Box 107)
  - TOM PAINE TREATMENT NO.1 FOR A FILM BY LEONARD LESLEY., Folder 3 (Box Box 107)
  - TOM PAINE TREATMENT NO.1 FOR A FILM BY LEONARD LESLEY., Folder 4 (Box Box 107)
  - TOWER BEYOND TRAGEDY SCRIPT., Folder 5 (Box Box 107)
  - UNKNOWN SOLDIER SCRIPT., Folder 6 (Box Box 107)
  - HAMLET /A EUROPE., Folder 1 (Box Box 108)
  - HAMLET /B EUROPE., Folder 2 (Box Box 108)
  - AMLET /B EUROPE., Folder 3 (Box Box 108)
  - SOUTH WEST TOUR., Folder 4 (Box Box 108)
  - FAUST., Folder 5 (Box Box 108)
  - PR (PERSONAL) GEN., Folder 6 (Box Box 108)
  - PR (PERSONAL) BREEN 1., Folder 7 (Box Box 108)
  - MEETINGS., Folder 8 (Box Box 108)
  - UNIDENTIFIED., Folder 9 (Box Box 108)
  - SLIDES (PORGY AND BESS, HAMLET, POSTCARDS)., Folder 1 (Box Box 109)
  - MEETINGS (BREENS, PORGY AND BESS CAST, ETC)., Folder 2 (Box Box 109)
  - PORGY AND BESS COSTUMES., Folder 3 (Box Box 109)
  - PORGY AND BESS POSTERS (PHOTOGRAPHS)., Folder 4 (Box Box 109)
  - PORGY AND BESS - SET DESIGN PHOTOGRAPHS., Folder 5 (Box Box 109)
  - PORGY AND BESS - PLAY (PHOTOGRAPHS)., Folder 6 (Box Box 109)
  - MISCELLANEOUS PLAY (PHOTOGRAPHS)., Folder 7 (Box Box 109)
  - POSTCARD., Folder 8 (Box Box 109)
  - 35 MM SLIDES: PORGY AND BESS., Folder 9 (Box Box 109)
  - 35 MM SLIDES: PORGY AND BESS., Folder 10 (Box Box 109)
  - DESKAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1941., Folder 1 (Box Box 110)
  - DESKAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1942., Folder 2 (Box Box 110)
  - DESK CALENDER AND DIARY 1941., Folder 3 (Box Box 110)
  - DESKAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1940., Folder 4 (Box Box 110)
  - DESK PRIVATE 1939., Folder 5 (Box Box 110)
  - INDIAN WALK 1935., Folder 6 (Box Box 110)
  - DESK CALENDER AND DIARY 1946., Folder 1 (Box Box 111)
  - RB 1946 "ENGAGEMENTS"., Folder 2 (Box Box 111)
  - DAY BY DAY., Folder 3 (Box Box 111)
  - 1945 "DESK CALENDER AND DIARY"., Folder 4 (Box Box 111)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1943., Folder 5 (Box Box 111)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1944., Folder 6 (Box Box 111)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1975., Folder 1 (Box Box 112)
  - APPOINTMENTS AND ADDRESSES 1974., Folder 2 (Box Box 112)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1974., Folder 3 (Box Box 112)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1973, Folder 4 (Box Box 112)
  - APPOINTMENTS AND ADDRESSES 1973., Folder 5 (Box Box 112)
  - DAILYAIDE THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1972., Folder 6 (Box Box 112)
  - APPOINTMENTS 1972., Folder 1 (Box Box 113)
  - APPOINTMENTS AND ADDRESSES 1971., Folder 2 (Box Box 113)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1971., Folder 3 (Box Box 113)
  - APPOINTMENTS 1970., Folder 4 (Box Box 113)
  - 1970 YEARBOOK., Folder 5 (Box Box 113)
  - 1969 YEARBOOK., Folder 6 (Box Box 113)
  - DAIYAIDE"THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1968., Folder 7 (Box Box 113)
  - 1983., Folder 1 (Box Box 114)
  - HAMLET /A EUROPE., Folder 1 (Box Box 108)
  - 1981., Folder 2 (Box Box 114)
  - 1980., Folder 3 (Box Box 114)
  - 1979., Folder 4 (Box Box 114)
  - DESK MASTER DAIRY 1976., Folder 1 (Box Box 115)
  - DESK MASTER DAIRY 1978., Folder 2 (Box Box 115)
  - THE DESK MASTER DAIRY 1977., Folder 3 (Box Box 115)
  - DESK MASTER DAIRY 1976., Folder 4 (Box Box 115)
  - DAILYAIDE "THE SILENT SECRETARY" 1976., Folder 5 (Box Box 115)
  - APPOINTMENTS AND ADDRESSES 1976., Folder 6 (Box Box 115)
  - APPOINTMENTS AND ADDRESSES 1975., Folder 7 (Box Box 115)
  - WILVA DAVIS BREEN/ RICHARD COL 22 OCT 1987 #4., Folder 1 (Box Box 116)
  - WILVA DAVIS BREEN/ RICHARD COL 22 OCT 1987 #5., Folder 2 (Box Box 116)
  - WILVA DAVIS BREEN INTERVIEW #3., Folder 3 (Box Box 116)
  - WILVA DAVIS BREEN INTERVIEW #2., Folder 4 (Box Box 116)
  - WILVA DAVIS BREEN INTERVIEW #1., Folder 5 (Box Box 116)
  - DAVIS BREEN #1 (TAPE)., Folder 7 (Box Box 116)
  - DAVIS BREEN #2 (TAPE)., Folder 8 (Box Box 116)
  - DAVIS BREEN #3 (TAPE)., Folder 9 (Box Box 116)
  - DAVIS BREEN #4 (TAPE)., Folder 10 (Box Box 116)
  - WILVA / MKS TOHWSON / R OE 22 OCT 1987., Folder 11 (Box Box 116)
  - EXPERIMENTAL THEATER CASTS AND STAFF., Folder 1 (Box Box 117)
  - ANTA MEMBERSHIP - BY STATE., Folder 1 (Box Box 118)
  - FILE #1., Folder 1 (Box Box 119)
  - FILE #1 (CONTINUED)., Folder 1 (Box Box 120)
  - BREEN PRINTS OVERSIZE A., Folder 1 (Box Box 121)
  - BREEN - PRINTS OVERSIZE., Folder 1 (Box Box 122)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 1 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 2 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 3 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 4 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 5 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 6 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 7 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 8 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 9 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 10 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 11 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA HAMLET., Folder 12 (Box Box 123)
  - ANTA NBC. TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE POSTERS., Folder 1 (Box Box 124)
  - ANTA SCRAPBOOK., Folder 1 (Box Box 125)
  - ANTA SCRAPBOOK., Folder 1 (Box Box 126)
  - PORGY AND BESS. AMERICAN NATIONAL BALLET THEATER ANTA SCRAPBOOKS., Folder 1 (Box Box 127)
  - FTP - COLLECTIONS., Folder 1 (Box Box 128)
  - ANTA., Folder 2 (Box Box 128)
  - "A CLOSE LOOK AT THE BIRTH OF THE BABY A.N.T." WASHINGTON THEATER GUIDE SUMMER/FALL 1985., Folder 1 (Box Box 129)
  - ANTA MAGAZINE, SPRING 1948., Folder 2 (Box Box 129)
  - "TOWERED A NATIONAL THEATER., Folder 3 (Box Box 129)
  - WORK AND PURPOSES OF ANTA., Folder 4 (Box Box 129)
  - "PORGY AND BESS IN RUSSIA" THE NEW YORKER, OCT, 27, 1956., Folder 5 (Box Box 129)
  - ANTA MAGAZINE, SPRING 1948., Folder 6 (Box Box 129)
  - MISS HARGREAVES., Folder 7 (Box Box 129)
  - "UNKNOWN SOLDIER"TREATMENT FOR FILM", Folder 8 (Box Box 129)
  - HELEN HAYES (PUBLIC RELATIONS)., Folder 1 (Box Box 130)
  - OUTGOING ANTA CORRESPONDENCE 1951 FEB. TO MARCH., Folder 2 (Box Box 130)
  - PROMOTON OF "BILLY BUB"., Folder 3 (Box Box 130)
  - CORRESPONDENCE FROM ELIE EDSON., Folder 4 (Box Box 130)
  - HAMLET ETC. 1949 NEWSPAPER CLIPPS., Folder 1 (Box Box 131)
  - HAMLET NEWS CLIPPS., Folder 2 (Box Box 131)
  - LAVIS JAUVET " THE SCHOOL FOR WIVES"., Folder 3 (Box Box 131)
  - MISC. TO JOUVET., Folder 4 (Box Box 131)
  - ANTA PRESS RELATIONS (FRAGILE)., Folder 5 (Box Box 131)
  - PUBLIC PAPERS ABOUT "THE SCHOOL, FOR WIVES"., Folder 6 (Box Box 131)
  - SANN - YANK SERVICE., Folder 7 (Box Box 131)
  - FRAGILE (PRESERVATION)., Folder 8 (Box Box 131)
  - ANTA BOARD MINUTES FEB. 1937 - NOV. 1945., Folder 1 (Box Box 132)
  - ANTA BOARD MINUTES FEB. 1946 - DEC. 1946., Folder 2 (Box Box 132)
  - LOGS 1946 - 1947., Folder 3 (Box Box 132)
  - BARTER THEATER., Folder 1 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE (UNDATED)., Folder 2 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE (1938)., Folder 3 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE (1944)., Folder 4 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE (1945)., Folder 5 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE 1947)., Folder 6 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE (1948)., Folder 7 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD / BREEN CORRESPONDENCE (1951)., Folder 8 (Box Box 133)
  - VETERANS THEATER (INC)., Folder 9 (Box Box 133)
  - DRAMA REPORT OF ROBERT PORTERFIELD., Folder 10 (Box Box 133)
  - FILE #4 ROBERT PORTERFIELD., Folder 11 (Box Box 133)
  - PORTERFIELD, BREEN PLAN WILVA DAVIS - CORRESPONDENCE., Folder 12 (Box Box 133)
  - PRESERVATION COPY., Folder 13 (Box Box 133)
  - ANTA (VERY EARLY 1945 - 46) WD AND RB'S NOTES, ETC., Folder 14 (Box Box 133)
  - 40'S (CORRESPONDENCE)., Folder 15 (Box Box 133)
  - WAR TIME (ARMY)., Folder 16 (Box Box 133)
  - COPIES OF RECORDS REMOVED DURING THE 80'S RE: FOUNDATION PLAN 1945 - 1948., Folder 17 (Box Box 133)
  - JAVITS (CORRESPONDENCE 1945 - 1950., Folder 18 (Box Box 133)
  - ANTA 1935., Folder 19 (Box Box 133)
  - NO TITLE (LETTERS W. DAVIS 6/12/2, 12/11/44, ESSAY THE HOME TOWN THEATER., Folder 20 (Box Box 133)
  - ANTA (MISC. 51 - 89)., Folder 21 (Box Box 133)
  - 50's., Folder 22 (Box Box 133)
  - HAMLET SUITE (KRUETZ) JULY 1949., Folder 1 (Box Box 134)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 2 (Box Box 134)
  - SEAN O' FEY OCT. 14, 1970., Folder 3 (Box Box 134)
  - BLUES OP COPY (1)., Folder 4 (Box Box 134)
  - BLUES OP COPY (3)., Folder 5 (Box Box 134)
  - S. MEYER - RB BLUES JUNE 18TH, 1956., Folder 6 (Box Box 134)
  - IRENE., Folder 7 (Box Box 134)
  - CLASSICAL., Folder 8 (Box Box 134)
  - BLUES OP COPY (2)., Folder 9 (Box Box 134)
  - NOV. BLUES NOV. 30, 1957., Folder 10 (Box Box 134)
  - PORGY AND BESS JUNE 21, 1955., Folder 11 (Box Box 134)
  - ARLEN ( NON - MERCER)., Folder 12 (Box Box 134)
  - BLUES OPERA - SPECIAL COPY (2)., Folder 13 (Box Box 134)
  - CHORAL., Folder 14 (Box Box 134)
  - ZURICH SOUNDTRACK CURTAIN CALLS JUNE 1955., Folder 15 (Box Box 134)
  - AMSTERDAM CURTAIN CALLS JUNE 3, 1956., Folder 16 (Box Box 134)
  - INTERVIEW FOR RADIO LIBERATION MARCH 1956., Folder 17 (Box Box 134)
  - B. DAVIS MARCH 27, 1956., Folder 18 (Box Box 134)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 19 (Box Box 134)
  - BLUES OP COPY (4)., Folder 20 (Box Box 134)
  - PORGY AND BESS WORKTAOE DEC. BERLIN., Folder 21 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B PART II SAN FRANCISCO., Folder 22 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B PART II SAN FRANCISCO #3., Folder 23 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B PART II SAN FRANCISCO #2., Folder 24 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B PART I SAN FRANCISCO #1., Folder 25 (Box Box 134)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 25 (Box Box 134)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 26 (Box Box 134)
  - COME RAIN OR SHINE., Folder 27 (Box Box 134)
  - VOICE OF AMERICA - ARMED FORCE NETWORK., Folder 28 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B CONCERT NOV. 23, 1955, Folder 29 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B WORKTAPE., Folder 30 (Box Box 134)
  - PIANO AND MALE VOICE., Folder 31 (Box Box 134)
  - P AND B 3 REELS - PART I AND FINAL ACT., Folder 32 (Box Box 134)
  - 2 ROLLS 35MM NEGATIVES UNIDENTIFIED., Folder 33 (Box Box 134)
  - BLUES OP COPY DEC. 1954 - 3rd COPY, REEL 4., Folder 1 (Box Box 135)
  - P AND B COMPOSITE JAN, 1957., Folder 2 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES II APRIL., Folder 3 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES OPERA., Folder 4 (Box Box 135)
  - FREE AND EASY (ARLEN) BLUES OPERA - AMSTERDAM DEC.., Folder 5 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES OP COPY DEC. REEL # 1., Folder 6 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES OP COPY DEC. REEL # 2., Folder 7 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES OP COPY DEC. REEL # 3., Folder 8 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES OPERA SPECIAL COPY REEL # 1., Folder 9 (Box Box 135)
  - BLUES OPERA SPECIAL COPY REEL # 3., Folder 10 (Box Box 135)
  - P AND B, S. MEYER - RB APRIL 1956., Folder 11 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN JUNE 26, 1959., Folder 12 (Box Box 135)
  - S. MEYER TO RB MARCH 29, 1956., Folder 13 (Box Box 135)
  - PLAYER PIANO., Folder 14 (Box Box 135)
  - FREE AND EASY (BLUES OPERA) AMSTERDAM - DEC. 1954., Folder 15 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN - SOBEL., Folder 16 (Box Box 135)
  - RB - SCHWITZER FALL 1954., Folder 17 (Box Box 135)
  - F AND E JUNE 1959., Folder 18 (Box Box 135)
  - NBC DISCUSSION - "SHOULD USA HOUSE A NATIONAL THEATER"., Folder 19 (Box Box 135)
  - TV NOTES RB - SCHAFFER SEPT. 17, 1955., Folder 20 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN (TV) JUNE 20, 1954., Folder 21 (Box Box 135)
  - BOB AND JORE DUSTIN SONGS NOV. 1956., Folder 22 (Box Box 135)
  - STARK - NO DATE., Folder 24 (Box Box 135)
  - BLANK REEL., Folder 25 (Box Box 135)
  - F AND E JEN - THRU KILLING JUNE 1954., Folder 26 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN SPIRITUALS., Folder 27 (Box Box 135)
  - KURT WEIL (7 DEADLY SINS)., Folder 28 (Box Box 135)
  - FREE AND EASY QUINCY JONES 8/25/59., Folder 29 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED - 1955., Folder 30 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 31 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 32 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 33 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN (PRIVATE RECORDINGS) 1954., Folder 34 (Box Box 135)
  - WW - RC SCHWITZER 1/17/54., Folder 35 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN 12., Folder 36 (Box Box 135)
  - HAMLET AT ELSINORE APRIL 15, 1964., Folder 37 (Box Box 135)
  - EDITH PIAF., Folder 38 (Box Box 135)
  - PORGY AND BESS TAPE # 1 1956., Folder 39 (Box Box 135)
  - HAMLET OCT. 7, 1970., Folder 40 (Box Box 135)
  - ARLEN - ED SULLIVAN TV/MOM GOT AWAY OCTOBER 10, 1954., Folder 41 (Box Box 135)
  - COLUMBIA - P AND B TAPE # 3., Folder 42 (Box Box 135)
  - FRENCH SONGS., Folder 43 (Box Box 135)
  - MEASURE FOR MEASURE - AUG. 12, 1964., Folder 44 (Box Box 135)
  - OTHELLO DUBLIN GATE THEATER., Folder 45 (Box Box 135)
  - PHONE S. MEYER AND RB DEC. 12, 1956., Folder 46 (Box Box 135)
  - HARLOD ARLEN DELLA BALLAD SEPT. 1950., Folder 47 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 48 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 50 (Box Box 135)
  - COLE PORTER TRIBUTE (CBS) OCT. 6, 1956., Folder 51 (Box Box 135)
  - P AND B UNTITLED., Folder 52 (Box Box 135)
  - HAMLET (OLD)., Folder 53 (Box Box 135)
  - HARLOD ARLEN., Folder 54 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED - 6, Folder 55 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED AUDIO CASSETTES - 4., Folder 56 (Box Box 135)
  - SPECIAL TAPES - SENT TO JACQUES LESLIE MARCH 15, 1959., Folder 57 (Box Box 135)
  - COMMERCIAL ON BLUES - PAPER BAG., Folder 58 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 59 (Box Box 135)
  - FREE AND EASY., Folder 60 (Box Box 135)
  - UNTITLED., Folder 61 (Box Box 135)
  - LAST LIVING NEWSPAPER (MOTION PICTURE) 16MM FILM., Folder 1 (Box Box 136)
  - MARION DAVIS' NEPHEW., Folder 2 (Box Box 136)
  - NBC GERSHWIN SALUTE., Folder 3 (Box Box 136)
  - BD AND RB ("SIGNING')., Folder 4 (Box Box 136)
  - ADAM CREATOR 9/23/60., Folder 5 (Box Box 136)
  - MARLENE DIETRICH IN LONDON., Folder 6 (Box Box 136)
  - ARLEN - PRIVATE RECORDINGS., Folder 7 (Box Box 136)
  - ROBERT BREEN MEMORIAL TAPE 4/28/90., Folder 8 (Box Box 136)